[upbeat rock music]
- You're never gonna get away with this, Dr. Shark Eyes.
- 你永远逃不掉，鲨鱼眼博士。
- Oh, I already have, Agent Maxwell.
- 哦，我已经逃掉了，麦斯威尔特工。
[cackling]
- These Jett Masterson spy movies are ridiculous.
- 这些杰特·马斯特森间谍电影太荒谬了。
- Ridiculously good.
- 荒谬得好。
Jett Masterson as Agent Zachary Maxwell
杰特·马斯特森饰演特工扎卡里·麦斯威尔
is the greatest spy that ever lived.
是有史以来最伟大的间谍。
- I feel safer living in a world that he protects.
- 有他保护的世界让我感到更安全。
- It's a movie, doofuses.
- 那是电影，傻瓜们。
There's no such thing as evil masterminds
不存在什么邪恶的幕后黑手
with pet sharks.
还养着宠物鲨鱼。
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
[murmurs]
[低语]
[shouts] - Crikey!
[大喊] - 天哪！
It bit him right in the face!
它直接咬了他的脸！
- Please. He gets bit in the face
- 拜托。他每部电影都被咬脸。
in every movie.
- 这不是菲尼厄斯。
- This isn't Finneas.
菲尼厄斯绝不会咬我！
Finneas would never bite me!
[喘息] 你换了我的鲨鱼，对吧？
[breathing raggedly]
You switched my shark, didn't you?
你换了我的鲨鱼，对吧？
- No. I hypnotized him.
不，我催眠了他。
You're not the only one with shark eyes.
不止你一个人有鲨鱼眼。
[extended dramatic sting]
♪ ♪
[together] Yes!
是的！
- He hypnotized the shark again.
他又催眠了鲨鱼。
These movies are all the same!
这些电影都一个样！
- You bite your tongue. - I can have an opinion.
你别说话。我有权发表意见。
- No, that's the next line of dialogue.
不，那是下一句对话。
- You bite your tongue.
你别说了。
- See?
看吧？
- You know who I blame for us being stuck
你知道我怪谁让我们在周六晚上
watching this marathon of garbage
看这些垃圾马拉松电影吗？我们的朋友！
on a Saturday night? Our friends!
我简直不敢相信他们都有医生预约。
I can't believe they all had doctor's appointments.
对今晚的无聊感到抱歉，布里特。
[scoffs] Sorry about this lame night, Britt.
布里特？
Britt?
电视响了
[television beeps] both: Hey!
嘿！
- Where'd Britt go?
- Britt去哪儿了？
- I don't know. He was here
- 我不知道。他一开始还在这里
when we started the marathon.
当我们开始马拉松的时候。
- Now will you unpause it, please?
- 现在你能取消暂停吗？
- Yeah. [television beeps]
- 好的。
- Ooh, a tongue will be bitten.
- 哦，有人要咬舌头了。
The question is...
问题是...
whose?
谁的？
[television beeps]
[together] Hey!
嘿！
- Where do you think Britt went?
- 你觉得布里特去哪儿了？
- You tell us.
- 你告诉我们。
You're the one who wasn't paying attention
你是那个没注意看那部“荒谬”电影的人。
to the "ridiculous" movie.
还是说你注意了？
Or were you?
- 承认吧。
- Admit it.
你真的很喜欢这部电影。
You really like this movie.
- 我才不喜欢。
- I do not. - Fine.
- 好吧。
Then we'll just have to get the truth out of you,
那我们就只好用麦斯韦尔探员的方式来逼你说出真相了。
Agent Maxwell style.
♪ ♪
[extended dramatic sting]
- Fine, I love these movies.
- 好吧，我确实喜欢这些电影。
But I still wanna know where Britt is.
- 但我还是想知道布里特在哪里。
- Maybe he went to bed. - Yeah, it's not like he had
- 也许他去睡觉了。
Saturday night plans without us.
- 是啊，不像他有周六晚上的计划不带我们。
- She said "didgeridoo,"
- 她说‘迪吉里杜管’，
and then I said, "more like didgeri-don't."
- 然后我说，‘更像是不想迪吉里杜’。
[all laughing]
[大家都在笑]
Oh. Hey, guys.
- 哦。嘿，伙计们。
- [sing-song] Awkward!
- [唱歌般] 尴尬！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[cheerful music]
[欢快音乐]
- What's going on?
- 怎么了？
The four of you said you couldn't hang out tonight
你们四个说今晚不能出来玩
because you all had doctor's appointments.
因为你们都说今晚不能出来。
- Explain yourselves.
- 解释一下。
- Well, it's a real coincidence.
- 嗯，真是巧合。
I had a toothache. - I had a stomachache.
我牙疼。 - 我胃疼。
- And I had a none-of-your-business ache.
- 而我有个不关你事疼。
- Physical therapy.
- 物理治疗。
- It turned out that all of our doctor's appointments
- 结果我们所有人的医生预约
happened to be in the Quincy Medical Building.
都碰巧在昆西医疗大楼。
- So when we were finished, we all met up
- 所以我们结束后，我们都聚在一起
with Britt in the lobby for, you know,
在大厅和布里特一起，你知道的，
after-appointment root beer floats.
预约后的根啤浮雪。
- Like you do.
就像你做的那样。
- Well, would you look at the time?
哎呀，看看时间？
We should get going.
我们该走了。
- I'll see you out.
我送你们出去。
- Something doesn't seem right with their story.
他们的故事似乎有些不对劲。
- Was it that they all had doctor's appointments
是因为他们都在周六晚上有医生预约吗？
on a Saturday night?
不，那是有可能的。
- No, that could happen.
是他们恰好在大厅相遇吗？
- Is it that they all just happened
这仍然在可能范围内。
to meet in the lobby?
他们恰巧在大厅相遇？
- Still in the realm of possibility.
- 这还在可能范围内。
- Is it that Miles doesn't actually have a watch?
- 是不是Miles其实没有手表？
- Yes! And it's the root beer floats.
- 对！还有那根啤酒冰淇淋。
Everyone knows you only go
大家都知道，去昆西医疗大楼
to the Quincy Medical Building for cheesesteaks.
只是为了吃芝士牛排。
- Good point. - They are delicious.
- 说得好。- 它们确实美味。
- Oh, here comes Britt.
- 哦，Britt来了。
Let's get to the bottom of this.
让我们揭开真相。
- I'll handle the interrogation...
- 我来负责审问...
Agent Maxwell style.
以Maxwell探员的方式。
Hey! Not so fast, Britt.
嘿！别那么快，Britt。
- Sorry. I'll close it slower next time.
- 抱歉。下次我会关慢点。
- Not the door. You.
- 不是门。是你。
How'd you hook up with our friends tonight...
今晚你是怎么和我们这些朋友搭上线的...
- At the Quincy Medical Building...
- 在Quincy医疗大楼...
- For root beer floats?
- 为了根汁啤酒冰淇淋？
[extended dramatic sting]
[延长戏剧性音效]
♪ ♪
- I said I'll handle it.
- 我说了我来处理。
- You don't own Agent Maxwell style.
- 你没有Maxwell特工的风格。
- Guys, no worries.
- 伙计们，别担心。
They sent a group text inviting everyone.
他们群发了短信邀请所有人。
You must have missed it while you were watching
你肯定是在看电影马拉松时没注意到。
your movie marathon.
我想我还是悄悄离开，不打扰你。
I figured I'd just slip out
真贴心！
and not bother you.
你太好了。
- Aw. - So thoughtful!
那么，如果没有其他问题，
- You're the best.
我要去睡了。
- Well, if there's no more questions,
晚安！明早见。
I'll turn in.
我要去睡了。
- Good night! - See you in the morning.
晚安！明天见。
- Dream about great things.
做个好梦。
Man, a group text? Makes perfect sense.
群发短信？说得通。
- Yeah, Britt would never do us like that.
是啊，布里特绝不会那样对我们。
- Uh, guys? There's no group text.
呃，伙计们？没有群发短信。
- Britt did us like that!
布里特就是那样对我们的！
- Relax. I'll just group-text
放松。我只会群发短信
our friends and ask what's up.
给我们的朋友，问问怎么回事。
- There will be no group text. I have questions,
不会有群发短信的。我有问题，
and I wanna look them in their eyes when they answer.
我想在他们回答时直视他们的眼睛。
- The only answer I want now is how to get a cheesesteak.
- 我现在唯一想知道的答案是如何弄到一份芝士牛排。
I wonder if I can get an appointment with Dr. Allred.
我想知道我能否预约到奥尔雷德医生。
♪ ♪
- Hey, look who it is! All our friends.
- 嘿，看看这是谁！我们所有的朋友。
- Hey, who's thirsty?
- 嘿，谁渴了？
How about some root beer floats?
来点根汁啤酒冰淇淋怎么样？
[fingers snapping] Oh, waitress!
[打响指] 哦，服务员！
- [sighs pleasantly] Enjoy your floats.
- [愉快地叹息] 享受你们的冰淇淋。
Snap at me again and you will never snap again.
再对我打响指，你就别想再打响指了。
- Sorry, Mom. It was just
对不起，妈妈。只是为了增加戏剧效果。
for dramatic effect.
为了戏剧效果。
Oh--I'm also gonna say "thanks, Toots" when you leave.
哦——我还会在你离开时说“谢谢，小妞”。
- No, you're not.
不，你不会的。
- Before you drink, a toast:
在你喝之前，我们来干杯：
To all the times we've hung out together.
为了我们一起度过的所有时光。
- The fun times, the special times.
那些快乐的时光，特别的时光。
- Like the time last night,
就像昨晚，
when we all got together and had root beer floats.
我们大家聚在一起喝根啤浮冰的时候。
- You guys weren't there.
你们不在那里。
- Exactly! Waitress!
- 没错！服务员！
Take away these root beer floats!
把这些根啤浮冰拿走！
- Hey, kids. Your mom wanted me to say,
- 嘿，孩子们。你们的妈妈让我转告，
"Clap at me again and you will never clap again."
“再对我鼓掌，你们就再也鼓不了掌了。”
But she did say you could "Toots" me?
但她确实说过你们可以“图茨”我？
[mumbles skeptically]
[怀疑地咕哝]
- Thanks, Toots.
- 谢谢，图茨。
- So why did you guys shut us out
- 那你们为什么把我们排除在群聊之外？
of the group text?
- 我们没有发起那个群聊。
- We didn't start that group text.
- 是的，是布里特。
- Yeah, it was Britt.
是啊，是Britt。
- Britt?
Britt？
- I think Miles was pretty clear.
我觉得Miles已经说得很清楚了。
- Come on, guys. Let's go get our floats back.
好了，伙计们，我们去找回我们的漂浮物吧。
Hey, Toots!
嘿，Toots！
- So Britt started that group text?
所以是Britt发起的那个群聊？
That's weird.
这有点奇怪。
- Yeah, Britt said
是的，Britt说
he was the receiver of the text,
他是收到短信的人，
not the sender.
不是发送者。
- Is it possible that Britt doesn't want to
- 会不会是Britt不想和我们一起出去？
hang out with us?
一起] 不可能。
[together] Nah.
我们俩: 不可能是我们。
both: It can't be us.
一定是...她。
It must be...her.
- 不可能是我。
- It can't be me.
一定是...他们。
It must be...them.
[延长戏剧性音效]
[extended dramatic sting]
♪ ♪
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
[upbeat rock music]
- ♪ Oh, oh, hey, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦，嘿，♪
- Hey, Britt.
嘿，布里特。
Eating cheese and crackers, huh?
在吃奶酪和饼干，嗯？
- Yup.
是的。
- You know, a lot of people think
你知道，很多人认为
me and my brothers are just like cheese and crackers.
我和我的兄弟们就像奶酪和饼干一样。
Always together. But not true.
总是形影不离。但事实并非如此。
In fact, you can have the cheese
实际上，你可以只有奶酪
without the crackers. You know what I'm saying?
而没有饼干。你明白我的意思吗？
- No, they're meant to be together.
不，它们是注定要在一起的。
That's why they put the cheese and biscuits
这就是为什么他们把奶酪和饼干
in the same package.
放在同一包里。
- [chuckles] Well, just because
- [笑声] 好吧，只是因为它们装在一起
they're in the same package doesn't mean
并不意味着你必须同时吃。
you have to eat them at the same time.
我的意思是，你现在可以吃奶酪
I mean, you could have the cheese now
然后永远不用搭理那两块无聊的饼干。
and never hang out with those two boring biscuits ever.
- 哦，我知道这是怎么回事了。
- Oh, I know what this is about.
给，拿走我的饼干。
Here, take my biscuits.
- 我不要饼干。
- I don't want the biscuits.
- 奶酪？ - 不。
- The cheese? - No.
- The little red stick?
- 那个小红棍？
- [sighs] No!
- [叹气] 不！
I wanna hang out with you
我想和你单独出去玩
without my brothers. How about tonight?
不带我兄弟。今晚怎么样？
- Oh, I can't.
- 哦，我不行。
I already have plans with Nicky and Ricky.
我已经和尼基和里基有约了。
Sorry, Dawn. But here.
对不起，道恩。但这里。
Enjoy.
享受吧。
- It was me he didn't want to hang out with!
- 他不想和我出去玩！
[struggles, sighs]
[挣扎，叹气]
- Hey, Britt! Hold up a sec.
- 嘿，布里特！稍等一下。
- Ooh, getting a jacket, huh? Might be chilly.
- 哦，拿外套啊？可能会冷。
Speaking of chilly,
说到冷，
how about the three of us...
我们三个...
"chill" together tonight?
今晚一起“冷”一下怎么样？
- I can't, mates.
- 不行，伙计们。
I'm "chilling" with Dawn tonight.
我今晚要和Dawn“冷”一下。
See ya!
再见！
- Wait...if he's already doing something
- 等等...如果他今晚已经和Dawn有安排了，
with Dawn tonight, then it was us!
既然他今晚和Dawn有约，那原本应该是我们！
- So...what are you guys doing tonight?
- 那么...你们今晚打算做什么？
- Nothing. You?
- 没什么特别的。你呢？
- Nothing.
- 也没什么。
- Who are you doing nothing with?
- 你和谁一起无所事事？
- Nobody.
- 没人。
Who are you doing nothing with?
你和谁一起无所事事？
- Nobody.
- 没人。
- Well, if you won't admit it,
- 好吧，如果你不承认，
I'll just stand here and see
我就站在这里看看
if you're really doing nothing with nobody.
如果你真的和没人在一起无所事事。
- So will we.
- 我们也会。
- Well,
- 好吧，
clearly nobody is doing
显然没人和没人在一起什么都没做。
nothing with nobody.
- 那我们能别站这儿了吗？
- Then can we stop standing here?
我眼睛疼，腿也麻了。
My eyes hurt and my legs are asleep.
- [呼气] 是啊。- 我也是--哦！
- [exhaling] Yeah. - Mine too--oh!
[众人哼声]
[all grunting]
显然Britt对我们所有人都撒谎了。
Well, clearly Britt lied to all of us.
- [大声哼声] - 可是他为什么要分别对我们...说不同的谎呢？
- [grunts loudly] - But why would he tell us...
- [大声咕哝] - 但他为什么要对我们...
separate lies?
说不同的谎言？
- [pants] To turn us against each other.
- [喘气] 为了让我们互相猜疑。
- Why would he want to turn us against each other?
- 他为什么要让我们互相猜疑？
- Oh, feeling's coming back! - [shouts]
- 哦，感觉回来了！ - [大喊]
- Pins and needles, pins and needles!
- 针扎感，针扎感！
- Okay, okay, okay. - If we can find him,
- 好了，好了，好了。 - 如果我们能找到他，
we can ask him.
我们就可以问他。
I'm gonna locate him
我要用我的‘追踪我的朋友’应用
on my Track My Pals app.
定位他。
The blue dot is Britt.
蓝点是布里特。
- What are all the red dots?
- 那些红点都是什么？
- Oh, that one's Natlee. There's Miles...there's Mae!
- 哦，那个是纳特莉。那是迈尔斯...那是梅！
- They're moving towards the blue dot!
- 他们都在向蓝点移动！
- He's stealing all our pals!
- 他在偷走我们所有的朋友！
- That was his plan.
- 那就是他的计划。
Distract us by forcing us
通过强迫我们
into a two-hour stare down so our legs would fall asleep
进行两个小时的瞪眼比赛，让我们的腿睡着
while he invited everyone out to...
同时他邀请所有人去...
Root Beer Flo's.
根啤弗洛的店。
- Home to Boulder's best
- 这里是博尔德最好的
non-medical building root beer floats!
非医疗建筑根汁啤酒冰淇淋！
- He completely manipulated us!
- 他完全操纵了我们！
- Just like when Dr. Shark Eyes manipulated
- 就像鲨鱼眼博士在
Maxwell's fellow agents
机构垒球比赛结束时操纵
at the end of the agency softball game
马克斯韦尔的同事们
so he could take them out...
以便带他们去...
for pizza and karaoke.
吃披萨和唱卡拉OK。
- Little did they know,
- 他们不知道的是，
the microphone was poisoned.
麦克风被下毒了。
- "We are family" were the last words
“We are family”是他们唱的最后一句。
they ever sang.
他们再也没唱过歌。
[television playing faintly] - Shh!
[电视微弱播放声] - 嘘！
- Spoiler alert!
- 剧透警告！
- Then, after the game, I'm gonna take you all out...
- 然后，比赛结束后，我要带你们所有人出去...
for pizza and karaoke!
- 去吃披萨和唱卡拉OK！
[cackling]
[咯咯笑]
[extended dramatic sting]
[延长戏剧性音效]
♪ ♪
[together] Sorry.
[一起] 对不起。
♪ ♪
- I can't believe Britt lied to us.
我真不敢相信布里特对我们撒谎了。
I bet he's out enjoying root beer floats
我打赌他现在正和我们的朋友在外面享受根啤漂浮呢！
with our friends right now! - While we're stuck here,
而我们却困在这里，
not enjoying root beer floats without our friends.
没有和朋友一起享受根啤漂浮。
- Why don't we just order root beer floats?
我们为什么不直接点根啤漂浮呢？
- Why don't we just sing into poisoned microphones?
我们为什么不直接对着有毒的麦克风唱歌呢？
- Guys, let's not fight, because we are fam--
伙计们，我们别吵架了，因为我们是一家人——
- Don't say those words.
别提那些词。
- Nicky, Britt isn't an evil mastermind.
尼基，布里特不是什么邪恶的幕后黑手。
He's just a really ungrateful houseguest.
他只是个非常不知感恩的客人。
- Who's an ungrateful houseguest?
- 谁是个不知感恩的客人？
- Britt. He charmed all our friends
- 布里特。他迷住了我们所有的朋友
and now they only wanna hang out with him and not us.
现在他们只想和他一起玩，而不是我们。
- Yeah, he's way over the line, Toots.
- 是的，他太过分了，美女。
- Well, I'm sure there's a logical explanation.
- 嗯，我相信一定有合理的解释。
- Hmm, Toots is right.
- 嗯，美女说得对。
- [spluttering] You too?
- [语无伦次] 你也是？
- Hey, guys!
- 嘿，伙计们！
Hey, foreign exchange Mum and Pup!
嘿，外国交换妈妈和爸爸！
- Hey! How are you? - [laughing]
嘿！你好吗？
- You work at Get Sporty now?
你在Get Sporty工作了？
- Did you call them "Mum and Pup?"
你叫他们'妈妈和爸爸'吗？
- Is that a shark-tooth necklace?
那是鲨鱼牙齿项链吗？
- It's puka shells. Mum and Pup got it for me
这是普卡贝壳。妈妈和爸爸为我获得的月度员工奖而给我的
for being employee of the month.
你在这里工作多久了？
- How long have you been working here?
我今天刚开始。
- I started today. - He's that good.
他真的很厉害。
- So, Mum, Pup,
所以，妈妈，爸爸，
I've been reviewing the books, and I think I've figured out
我一直在审查账本，我想我已经找到了
a way to get a real bite out of some of the overhead.
找到了一种方法，可以真正削减一些固定开支。
- [whispering] Did you hear that?
- [低声] 你听到了吗？
He said "bite"! Like a shark!
他说了“咬”！就像鲨鱼一样！
- Uh, the kids don't care about all of this.
- 呃，孩子们不关心这些。
Let's discuss your ideas over some root beer floats.
我们边喝根啤冰淇淋边讨论你的想法吧。
- Yeah. Such a go-getter.
- 是啊。真是个积极进取的人。
You know, one day, this could be, "Britt's Get Sporty."
你知道吗，有一天，这可能会变成“布里特的运动天地”。
[all gasp]
[所有人都倒吸一口气]
- He's not just trying to steal our friends.
- 他不只是在试图抢走我们的朋友。
- And our family business.
- 还有我们的家族生意。
- And Mom and Toots!
还有妈妈和图茨！
- He's trying to steal our lives.
他试图偷走我们的生活。
[all laughing raucously]
（所有人哄笑）
- [laughing]
（笑）
[siblings shiver audibly]
（兄弟姐妹们发出颤抖的声音）
♪ ♪
- Where's Nicky? We have to figure out
尼基在哪儿？我们得解决这个布里特的问题。
this Britt situation.
我有好消息也有坏消息。
- I've got good news and I've got bad news.
坏消息是，奥尔雷德医生说我需要切除扁桃体。
Bad news is, Dr. Allred said I need my tonsils out.
好消息是什么？
- What's the good news? - I got cheesesteaks!
- 好消息是什么？ - 我买了芝士牛排！
- Okay, we need to get to the bottom
- 好的，我们需要彻底
of whether Britt is really an evil mastermind.
查明Britt是否真的是一个邪恶的幕后黑手。
- Yeah, what do we really even know about this guy?
- 是啊，我们对这家伙到底了解多少？
- We need to uncover the truth
- 我们需要揭露真相
and find out what his next move is.
并找出他的下一步行动。
- I got it!
- 我明白了！
In all the Agent Maxwell movies,
在所有的Maxwell特工电影中，
there's always a beautiful woman who's able
总有一个美丽的女人能够
to charm the information out of people.
从人们那里套出信息。
- I like it!
我喜欢这个主意！
Dawn, go get one of your dresses.
Dawn，去拿一件你的裙子。
And give it to Nicky!
然后给Nicky！
- What? That's ridiculous!
什么？这太荒谬了！
- Completely.
完全同意。
Give it to Ricky.
给Ricky。
- Uh, don't you think there's a better person
呃，你不觉得有更适合的人选吗？
for the job?
嗯，是的，但爸爸不在这里。
- Well, yeah, but Dad's not here.
我！我-我-我！
- Me! Me-me-me!
我应该是那个穿裙子的人！
I should be the one
我应该是那个
getting in the dress!
穿上这件衣服的人！
- [snorts]
哼
- Whatever.
随便吧。
- Okay.
好吧。
- Hello...Britt.
你好...布里特。
- Wow, Dawn. Look at you.
哇，唐，看看你。
- Yes, look at me.
是的，看看我。
[shouts]
哎呀！你还好吗？
- Crikey! Are you okay?
我没事。
- [exhales] I'm fine.
[grunts]
哼。
[together] Should've been you.
本该是你。
- Are you sure you're all right?
你确定你没事吗？
- Yes, I was just taking a little shortcut
是的，我只是抄了个小近路。
down the stairs.
下楼梯。
- Uh-oh. I think you may have
哎呀。我觉得你可能有点流鼻血。
a bit of a nosebleed.
哦。没事。
- Oh. All good.
喊。
[shouts]
所以，Britt...今晚有什么计划吗？
[in nasally voice] So, Britt...
[鼻音] 那么，布里特...
any plans for this evening?
今晚有什么计划吗？
Big plans, little plans,
大计划，小计划，
master plans?
还是主计划？
- No, but I do have a bit of homework
- 没有，但我确实有一些作业
to do upstairs.
要在楼上做。
- Oh, homework. Of course!
- 哦，作业。当然！
You have to feed that master mind of yours.
你得喂饱你那聪明的大脑。
So what are you studying?
那你学什么呢？
Math? Science?
数学？科学？
Betrayal?
背叛？
- Uh, no. Just history.
- 呃，不是。只是历史。
- History of betrayal?
- 背叛的历史？
- Nope. Regular history.
- 不。普通的历史。
- [chewing] Okay, what was that?
- [咀嚼] 好吧，那是什么？
- [chewing] Besides an epic fail.
- [咀嚼] 除了一个史诗级的失败。
- Is it an epic fail that I got him
- 我让他带着背包离开我们，这是不是个史诗级的失败？
to leave us alone with his backpack?
[extended dramatic sting]
♪ ♪
- Ugh. Can you...
- 呃。你能...
- Do you...
- 你...
- Ugh...
- 呃...
- All right.
- 好吧。
Let's see, what do we have here?
让我们看看，这里有什么？
[gasps] "Top secret"! What's he planning?
[吸气声] "绝密"！他在计划什么？
- It looks like a surprise party.
- 看起来像是一个惊喜派对。
- A surprise party with karaoke
- 一个有卡拉OK和毒麦克风的惊喜派对？
and poison microphones?
- 不，只是一个普通的无毒惊喜派对。
- No, just a regular poison-free surprise party.
- 这听起来并不那么邪恶。
- That doesn't sound so evil.
那听起来并不邪恶。
- But here's something that is:
但这里有个真正邪恶的事情：
We're not on the guest list.
我们不在宾客名单上。
- Wait. The only person not invited
等等。唯一一个没有被邀请
to a surprise party is the person
参加惊喜派对的人是
who the surprise party is for.
那个惊喜派对的主角。
- So it's for us?
所以这是为我们准备的？
- But why would he plan a surprise party for us?
但他为什么要为我们策划一个惊喜派对呢？
Our birthday is five months away.
我们的生日还有五个月呢。
- Well, that would be a good way to surprise us.
嗯，那倒是个让我们惊喜的好办法。
- He's not up to something evil.
- 他没有在策划什么坏事。
He's up to something nice.
他在策划一些好事。
- Who's up to something nice? [siblings shouting]
- 谁在策划好事？[兄弟姐妹们喊道]
- We are! - Putting stuff
- 是我们！ - 在你们背包里放东西！
into your backpack!
- 那些东西好像是自己掉出来的！ - 没错。
- Which seemed to have fallen out
- 看，我知道你看到了那个活页夹。
on its own! - Yeah.
我很抱歉。
- Look, I know you saw the binder.
我不想让你这样发现惊喜派对。
I'm so sorry.
没关系。
I didn't want you to find out
我们不会告诉任何人的。
about the surprise party like this.
关于惊喜派对这件事。
- It's okay. - We won't tell anybody.
- 没关系。 - 我们不会告诉任何人。
- And we'll act surprised when it happens.
- 而且我们会在派对上装作很惊喜。
Don't worry about that. I mean,
别担心那个。我是说，
look how good we are at it.
看看我们在这方面做得多好。
Really? - For us?
真的吗？ - 为我们自己？
- What?
- 什么？
- Oh, I think you've got it wrong.
- 哦，我想你搞错了。
The party isn't for you. It's for Avery.
派对不是为你准备的。是为了Avery。
- Really? - For Avery?
- 真的吗？ - 为了Avery？
- What?
什么？
- Her birthday's coming up, so...
她的生日快到了，所以...
- But we aren't on the guest list.
但我们不在宾客名单上。
- Yeah. - Sorry.
是啊。
If it's any consolation,
抱歉。
it was a hard decision.
如果这能让你好受些，
- [scoffs] I can't believe he's having a party
这真是个艰难的决定。
and not inviting us.
我真不敢相信他开派对却不邀请我们。
- Well, at least we know he's not an evil mastermind
嗯，至少我们知道他不是个邪恶的幕后黑手
trying to get rid of us.
试图摆脱我们。
- This to-do list fell out of Britt's backpack.
- 这份待办事项清单是从布里特的书包里掉出来的。
"Number one: get rid of the Quads."
"第一条：摆脱四胞胎。"
- He is an evil mastermind trying to get rid of us!
- 他是个邪恶的幕后黑手，想要除掉我们！
♪ ♪
- Let's not jump to conclusions.
- 我们别急着下结论。
"Get rid of the Quads" could mean anything.
"摆脱四胞胎"可能意味着任何事情。
- Number two is "take over Get Sporty."
- 第二条是"接管Get Sporty。"
- And number three is "celebrate"!
- 第三条是"庆祝"！
- Yeah, Britt wants us gone.
- 是的，布里特想让我们消失。
- What else is on that list?
- 那张清单上还有什么？
- Nothing. Why would he write anything after "celebrate"?
- 没什么。他为什么会在“庆祝”之后写东西？
- Why would an evil mastermind need
- 一个邪恶的大脑需要
to make a list with only three things?
制作一个只有三项的清单吗？
There's gotta be something on the back.
背面肯定有东西。
- There's nothing on the back. - Is something we can say once we've turned it over and looked at the back.
- 背面什么都没有。 - 这是我们在翻过来并看过背面后才能说的。
- I'm not turning it over.
- 我不会翻过来的。
- Can you believe this guy?
- 你能相信这家伙吗？
- Guys, stop!
- 伙计们，停下！
- Gah! - And now we'll never know.
- 啊！ - 现在我们永远不会知道了。
- [stammers] Who cares?
- [结巴] 谁在乎？
We need to find a way to expose him.
我们需要找到一个方法来揭露他。
- We need to figure out a way to get Britt
我们需要想出一个办法让布里特
to admit his diabolical plans in front of everyone.
在所有人面前承认他的邪恶计划。
- We could do it at Avery's party.
我们可以在艾弗里的派对上做这件事。
- Hm. - But we weren't invited.
但我们没有被邀请。
- That wouldn't stop Agent Zachary Maxwell.
那不会阻止扎卡里·马克斯韦尔特工。
And it's not gonna stop us.
也不会阻止我们。
- Yeah, we could do what he did to Dr. Shark Eyes
是的，我们可以像他在《只为鲨鱼眼》中对鲨鱼眼博士做的那样
at the end of "For Shark Eyes Only:"
让他失去行动能力，把他挂在鲨鱼池上
incapacitate him, hang him over a shark tank
直到他承认真相。
until he admits the truth.
- I get the shark and the dangling,
- 我明白鲨鱼和悬挂的部分，
but how are we gonna incapacitate him?
但我们要怎么让他失去行动能力？
- Hmm...oh, we could use one of Dicky's dirty socks.
- 嗯...哦，我们可以用迪基的一只脏袜子。
He left them everywhere when he went to Australia.
他去澳大利亚时到处乱扔。
I bet there's one in here.
我打赌这里有一只。
See?
看？
- Wait, how do we know it's still ripe?
- 等等，我们怎么知道它还是臭的？
It's ripe.
它很臭。
[male singer vocalizing]
♪ ♪
- Psst, Britt.
嘘，布里特。
- Hey, Dawn.
嘿，唐。
- [whistling]
（吹口哨）
kids: Surprise!
孩子们：惊喜！
- [shouting]
（喊叫）
- Sorry, Toots. False alarm.
对不起，小甜心。虚惊一场。
- [panting] It's okay.
（喘气）没事的。
It's okay. All right, see?
没事的。好了，看吧？
The cake's fine.
蛋糕没事。
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
That's the third time today!
这是今天第三次了！
- Well, then stop screaming "surprise"!
- 那你就别再大喊'惊喜'了！
- Hold on, guys. Where's Britt?
- 等等，伙计们。布里特在哪儿？
He's gonna miss the actual surprise.
他可别错过真正的惊喜。
- Everyone, stop what you're doing!
- 大家，都停下手中的事！
- Britt isn't who he says he is.
- 布里特并不是他所说的那样。
He's actually an evil mastermind
他实际上是一个邪恶的幕后黑手，
who came here to take over our lives.
来到这里是为了接管我们的生活。
- Your lives?
- 你们的生活？
[all laughing]
[所有人都在笑]
- We knew you wouldn't believe us.
- 我们知道你们不会相信我们。
So maybe you'll believe Britt himself.
所以也许你们会相信布里特自己。
[all gasp]
[所有人都惊讶地吸气]
- Britt!
- 布里特！
- [gasps] Didgeri-don't!
- [吸气]不要这样！
- Okay, Britt. Reveal your evil plan.
- 好吧，布里特。揭露你的邪恶计划。
- What's going on?
- 发生什么事了？
I don't have an evil plan.
- 我没有邪恶计划。
- We knew you wouldn't admit it.
- 我们知道你不会承认的。
Now things are about to get ugly.
现在事情要变得棘手了。
- What's that on his feet?
他脚上是什么？
- Peanut butter.
花生酱。
- How did he step in peanut butter?
他怎么踩到花生酱了？
- Peanut butter stepped on him.
是花生酱踩到他了。
- Wait, so is peanut butter, like, a guy or something?
等等，所以花生酱是个家伙还是什么？
- No, just regular peanut butter from a jar.
不，只是普通罐装的花生酱。
- Is it crunchy or creamy?
是脆的还是滑的？
- Okay, what does it matter?
好吧，这有什么关系？
[whistles] Sharky!
鲨鱼！
- [laughing]
- Anything to tell us now, "mate"?
- 现在有什么要告诉我们的吗，'伙计'？
- [gasping] Fine, I'll admit it!
- 好吧，我承认！
The truth is, the party isn't for Avery.
事实上，这个派对不是为Avery准备的。
It's for you.
是为你准备的。
- Yeah, even though it really is my birthday.
- 是的，尽管今天确实是我的生日。
[noisemaker squawks]
- [laughing] I wanted to thank you
我想感谢你们
for accepting me into your family.
接纳我成为你们家庭的一员。
You're the best brothers and sister a guy could have.
你们是最好的兄弟姐妹，一个家伙能拥有的。
all: Aww.
大家：哎呀。
- No "aww"s! Don't "aww"!
- 不要‘哎呀’！别‘哎呀’！
He's trying to trick you.
他在试图骗你们。
- Well, Britt,
- 那么，布里特，
if you really wanted to thank us
如果你真的想感谢我们
for being part of your family,
成为你家庭的一部分，
then what about your list?
那你的清单呢？
"One: get rid of the Quads."
第一条：摆脱四胞胎。
- [giggling] I needed to get rid of you guys
- [咯咯笑] 我需要摆脱你们
so I could plan your party.
这样我才能策划你们的派对。
[together] Oh.
哦。
- Well, what about number two?
那么，第二条呢？
"Take over Get Sporty"!
“接管Get Sporty”！
- Yeah, so we could decorate for your party.
是的，这样我们就可以为你的派对装饰了。
[together] Oh.
哦。
- Well, you certainly won't be able to explain number three.
好吧，你肯定无法解释第三条。
"Celebrate"--which, now that I say out loud,
“庆祝”——现在我大声说出来，
probably means celebrate for our party.
可能意味着为我们派对庆祝。
- Turn the list over. - Why?
把清单翻过来。
- "Trick Nicky, Ricky, and Dawn with a decoy party for Avery,
为什么？
then throw them the best surprise party ever."
然后给他们举办一个史上最棒的惊喜派对。
[together] Oh.
[一起] 哦。
- Seems like something that should be
- 看起来像是应该写在清单前面的内容，不过好吧。
on the front of a list, but okay.
- 我们都知道你们几个是守不住秘密的，所以计划是
- We all know you guys are impossible
让布里特偷偷溜走，带走你们所有的朋友，让你们起疑。
to keep a secret from, so the plan was
- 一旦你们开始四处打探，他就假装派对是为了艾弗里，
to make you suspicious by having Britt sneak off
我们知道你们会闯进来。
with all of your friends. - And once you guys started
- 这都是图茨的主意。
snooping around, he pretended the party was for Avery,
- [叹气]
which we knew you'd crash.
大家都在说这个吗？
- It was all Toots's idea. - [sighs]
- 这都是图茨的主意。 - [叹气]
Is everybody saying it?
大家都在这么说吗？
all: Yes.
所有人: 是的。
- So, I guess...
- 所以，我猜...
- Surprise, mates!
- 惊喜，伙计们！
- How'd you get out?
- 你们是怎么逃出来的？
- You covered me in peanut butter.
- 你用花生酱把我全身涂满了。
I slipped right out.
我就这么滑出来了。
- I can't believe you went to all that trouble, Britt.
- 我真不敢相信你费了这么大劲，布里特。
That was really nice. - Hm.
那真是太好了。 - 嗯。
- Oh--sorry we socked and peanut butter'd you.
哦——抱歉我们用袜子和花生酱对付了你。
- Yeah, it's the kind of thing we normally do
是啊，这是我们通常对
to our closest friends and family,
我们最亲近的朋友和家人做的事情，
so...welcome to the family.
所以...欢迎加入我们的家庭。
- [chuckles] And speaking of family,
[轻笑] 说到家庭，
let's get this party started with a little karaoke!
让我们用一点卡拉OK来开始这个派对吧！
[all cheering]
[众人欢呼]
Ah, this microphone's got a little dust on it.
啊，这个麦克风上有点灰尘。
- Is that Dicky's sock?
那是迪基的袜子吗？
- Our first number will be a little song
我们的第一首歌将是一首小曲
called "We Are Fa..."
叫做“我们是Fa...”
- Toots!
- 图茨！
- He'll be fine. - Yeah.
- 他会没事的。 - 是的。
[cheerful rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪